KEN MELETA FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER

WWW.KENMELETA.COM / 609-752-1633 / KMELETA@GMAIL.COM

SUMMARY

Front end web and UI developer with a strong appreciation for user experience and design. Fluent in HTML, CSS, and Javascript, with a working knowledge of several MVC frameworks. Excited to learn and adapt to every project and team's particular development stack.

EXPERIENCE

SENIOR FRONT END DEVELOPER

MIRUM AGENCY (FORMERLY DIGITARIA)

2012 - 2017

Utilized modern techniques and frameworks to deliver responsive and accessible websites against aggressive deadlines. I've lead and collaborated on the development of numerous large scale projects working alongside some of the best in the business.

WEB DESIGNER & DEVELOPER

FREELANCE 2007 - 2017

Work closely with clients to design and develop web solutions and brand identity.

SIMULATION DEVELOPER

LOCKHEED MARTIN MS2

2011 - 2012

Developed sophisticated government contracted training simulations, primarily utilizing the Adobe Flex and Flash frameworks, as well as HTML and Javascript.

FLASH & WEB DEVELOPER

HUMID DESIGN

2010

As a development intern, I conceptualized and developed visually complex Flash presentations and applications as well as front-end web development tasks with HTML, CSS, and Javascript.

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

KOVOD SIGNS & ENGRAVING

2006 - 2007

Designed marketable logos, signs, banners, artwork reproductions and other promotional items from scratch for various local companies while meeting strict deadlines.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN WEB DESIGN & INTERACTIVE MEDIA

THE ART INSTITUTE OF PHILADELPHIA

2010

Produced quality work in all classes including those focused around HTML / CSS, JavaScript / AJAX, PHP / MySQL and Adobe Photosop, while maintaining a 3.9 GPA.

PRIMARY SKILLS

HTML5 CSS3/SASS JAVASCRIPT/JQUERY GIT/SVN PHOTOSHOP ACTIONSCRIPT 3

SECONDARY SKILLS

BOOTSTRAP
GULP/GRUNT
ANGULAR 2
REACTJS
WORDPRESS
DRUPAL
PHP/MYSQL
SITECORE
ILLUSTRATOR
SKETCH